<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="str_trans">
        <item>There is none worthy of worship but Allah, Muhammad [peace be upon him] is the messenger of Allah.</item>
        <item>I bear witness that (there is) no god except Allah; One is He, no partner hath He, and I bear witness that Muhammad (Sall-Allahu Alayhi wa Sallam) is His Servant and Messenger.</item>
        <item>Flawless is Allah and the Praise is of Allah, and (there is) no god except Allah, and Allah is the Greatest. And (there is) neither might nor power except with Allah, the Sublime, the Tremendous.</item>
        <item>(There is) no god except Allah - One is He, no partners hath He. His is the Dominion, and His is the Praise. He gives life and causes death, and He is Living, who will not die, never. He of Majesty and Munificence. Within His Hand is (all) good. And He is, upon everything, Able (to exert His Will).</item>
        <item>I seek forgiveness from Allah, my Lord, from every sin I committed knowingly or unknowingly, secretly or openly, and I turn towards Him from the sin that I know and from the sin that I do not know. Certainly You, You (are) the knower of the hidden things and the Concealer (of) the mistakes and the Forgiver (of) the sins. And (there is) no power and no strength except from Allah, the Most High, the Most Great.</item>
        <item>O Allah! I seek protection in You from that I should not join any partner with You and I have knowledge of it. I seek Your forgiveness from that which I do not know. I repent from it (ignorance) and I reject disbelief (kufr) and joining partners with You (shirk) and of falsehood and slandering (gheebat) and innovation in religion (bid\'at) and tell-tales (nameemat) and bad, evil deeds (fawahish) and the blame and the disobedience, all of them. I submit to Your will and I believe and I declare: There is none worthy of worship except Allah and Muhammad( Peace Be Upon On Him) is His Messenger.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>